(Amy:)I think this is
the first time we've ever
(Amy:)actually been alone together.
(Howard:)Huh, I guess you're right.
Wonder why that is.
(Amy:)Well, off the top of my head,
I'd say we don't have a lot
(Amy:)in common except for the people
we're involved with.
(Amy:)Plus, when we first met,
Penny warned me never
(Amy:)to get into a car alone with you.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Howard:)You know, I bet you and I have
more in common than we think.
(Amy:)-Such as?
-I don't know.
-Tell me somethings you like.
-Uh, let's see.
(Amy:)I like harps,
Little House on the Prairie,
(Amy:)medieval poetry,
medieval literature--
(Howard:)Hey, how about some music?
(Amy:)Great. Sheldon never lets me
listen to music in the car.
(Amy:)He doesn't want to be mistaken
for a gang member.
(Howard:)Find something you like.
(Amy:)Beatles, boring.
(Amy:)Eminem, scary.
Weird AI? How old are you?
(Amy:)-Neil Diamond?
-Yeah, I love Neil Diamond.